muamat.com 2018-02-01

# 

**Privacy Policy**

We understand that you have confidential information and want you to know that muamat.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online, and that we strive to make our site as safe and secure as reasonably possible. If you have any questions after reading the statement, please let us know. We want to hear from you! You can email us by using our contact us form.

**Information Collection**  
During registration we ask for your name, country, state, zip/postal code, email address. In addition to the information we obtain at registration, we may ask you for information at other times, such as when you make a purchase or register for a service on muamat.com, when you submit a listing for a Web site, or when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. If you contact muamat.com we may keep a record of that correspondence. muamat.com also may occasionally ask you to provide information to participate in certain voluntary promotions, surveys, or contests (see the section regarding this below). Finally, muamat.com collects information about its Members in general, which does not necessarily identify the Member, using our server log files and some of the methods described under "cookies" below.

**Partner Services or Linked sites**  
Certain products and services available through muamat.com are made available by other companies with which muamat.com has a strategic alliance. To obtain some of these other products and services you may be on the other company's Web site or a site they share with muamat.com. When ordering, registering for, or purchasing products or services from these partners, you will be entering into an agreement with that partner, and not with muamat.com. In these cases, this privacy policy does not apply; instead, the privacy policy of the partner actually providing the goods or services will apply. We urge you to read and understand our partners' policies before entering into agreements with them. We are committed to partnering with companies that share our privacy concerns. muamat.com, however, can't control the way these partners collect or use information.

Also, when you click through to a partner's, an advertiser's, or other site linked from muamat.com, those companies may use cookies or other means to collect information about you. Again, this privacy policy does not apply to those sites; instead, the privacy policy of the site you visit will apply.

If you have questions about our partners' privacy policies or the privacy policies of these other sites, we encourage you to contact them directly.

**Why muamat.com collect my information**  
muamat.com uses your information to enable you to take advantage of the features available through the muamat.com site. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to muamat.com: you are given a muamat.com ID and are able to take full advantage of muamat.com many offerings. Additional information you volunteer enables us to better customize your experience. We may also use your contact information to reach you regarding important issues about the use of our service.

We use other information we collect to get a better understanding of our Member base. The more insight we have into you-the people who use muamat.com on a daily basis-the better we can serve you. Therefore, we analyze our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us through our Web site. Our research and analysis is done on an aggregate basis, and is not intend to identify individual Members.

**Sharing Information With Others**  
If you choose to receive information from our partners, muamat.com (or agents working on behalf of muamat.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. muamat.com will not provide your information to our partners unless it is necessary to complete a purchase of a partner or co-branded product/service on muamat.com that you have ordered. This may be necessary so that they may process your orders and ship, supply, maintain, or service the goods or services that you requested. If you register directly with another company reached through the muamat.com site, then that company will have control over the information you provide.

Also, please pay attention to which services you register for when you register for muamat.com. In some instances we have offered you the choice to register with certain of our partners at the same time you register at muamat.com. If you choose to register with a partner, the information that you provide in registration may also be provided to that partner and will be subject to our partner's privacy policy. Our partner's policies as to the use of information may differ from muamat.com policy. Again, we encourage you to review our partner's policies before you enter into agreements with them.

**Sponsors/Contests/Surveys**  
Information we obtain from voluntary programs such as surveys, promotions, and contests may be subject to additional or different terms, or may be used in a slightly different way. If different terms do apply, details of the shared use of this information will be outlined in the specific terms and conditions or rules of these special surveys, promotions, or contests. Please be sure to read those specific terms and conditions because they may alter what is written in this Privacy Policy on a case-by-case basis.

**Special Cases**  
muamat.com may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating muamat.com Terms of Use. The same policy applies in cases where we believe an individual may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) muamat.com rights or property, other muamat.com users or Members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. muamat.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. muamat.com may also display entity names as part of the registration process to facilitate an individual registrant�s affiliation with the correct entity.

**Cookies and Tracking Technology**  
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server, and gets saved on your computer hard drive. These cookie files store and sometimes track information about what you do on muamat.com. This information makes it possible for us to offer and provide highly customized services. All areas on muamat.com where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies in order for that part of the site to function.

muamat.com also collects IP Addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. In addition, muamat.com mail includes IP addresses in outgoing mail message headers.

You do have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences you can choose to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, however, you will be unable to use those muamat.com services that require registration in order to participate. These services include (but are not limited to): being able to view full news articles, printable versions of news articles and study guides, download our study guides in PDF format.

With most browsers you have an option to accept per-session cookies that are not stored on your computer and deleted as soon as you close your browser. If you don't want to accept cookies that are stored on your computer, you must at least accept per-session cookies in order to use our site to the full potential.

**Choices Regarding the Use of my Information**  
When you register with muamat.com, you can choose whether or not you want to receive information from us or from our partners. If you do not want to receive this information, be sure to indicate that on your muamat.com registration form. You also have choices about whether you want to receive this information when you visit and provide information to other sites, including sites accessible through muamat.com

**Cancelling my muamat.com Account**  
Your muamat.com account can be deleted or deactivated anytime. Once you do so, however, you won't be able to access any Members-only area of muamat.com, including your muamat.com Mail account. To delete your account, please contact admin@muamat.com and be sure to include your muamat.com Username. We will provide complete instructions on deleting or deactivating your muamat.com account. 

**Additional Information about your privacy**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online--for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas--that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
As muamat.com expands its offerings, we will update our Privacy Policy to address these changes. Please check this page on a regular basis for updates to this Privacy Policy.

**Questions or Suggestions**  
If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please email us using our contact us form. 

Last updated April 01, 2009
